

MARTIN PROVOST

Looking for a position as Social Media Ads / Traffic Manager

ABOUT ME

Ever since university, I have always been deeply interested in developing my creativity and learning more about technology. Over the last 6 years, I have launched different businesses (mostly start-ups and e-commerce projects) and built a strong entrepreneurial mindset.

Proactive, self-taught and autonomous, I like to implement strategies to help companies reach their customers more effectively: in the right place, at the right time, with the right message.

I have just completed @Le Wagon coding bootcamp (Paris, Batch #200 - dec 2018) to add technical skills to my profile.

I'm passionate about tech environment, growing my expertise fields and building beautiful things.

For more infos, please check my online resume: https://www.martin-provost.me

CONTACT

- +33 625056557
- martin@fansfinger.com
- 25 rue del'Armorique75015 Paris
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/martin-provost/
- hhttps://www.martin-provost.me

INTERESTS









EXPERIENCES

+ EAZYRIDE

2018 - 2018

WEB DEVELOPER

Eazyride was my team's final project during our time at Le Wagon. Eazyride is a carpooling platform geared towards sports activities. The driver brings his passengers on roundtrip journeys while sharing sports gear with them.

+ FANS FINGER

2017 - 2019

CEO / FOUNDER

Fans Finger is an e-commerce shop inspired by the famous American sports fan accessory, the #1 Foam Hand. Companies, clubs, organization and individuals can customize our foam hands with their own color, logo and text.

More than 100,000 foam hands printed and delivered and over 100 happy customers with only SEO , Social Media Ads (FB & IG) and automated email campaigns.

+ WE PLAY SPORT

2014 - 2017

CEO / CO-FOUNDER

We Play Sport was a crowdfunding platform for sports-related projects. Athletes, clubs, organizations and sports event organizers could launch fundraising campaigns.

80K€ fundraising from investors, management a team of 8 people, more than 250 helped projects and 800K€ raised on the platform.

SKILLS

WEB DEV

SOCIAL ADS

SEO/SEA

EMAILING

WEB ANALYTICS

WEB DESIGN

EDUCATION

+ LE WAGON - PARIS

2018 - 2018

WEB DEVELOPMENT

9-week intensive coding Bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails. Designed, Implemented and Shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of http://www.eazyride.co/

+ EDHEC BUSINESS SCHOOL - LILLE

2008 - 2012

MASTER DEGREE IN ENTREPRENEURSHIP

EDHEC Business School is a private French graduate business school, a 'Grandes Ecoles', specializing in business and management.